LEE WOEI PENG Curriculum Vitae

### **CAREER SUMMARY**

I have ten years of hands-on experience in various business roles with various achievements: Manufacturing (production, dealing with DOE and DOSH), Quality (QAQC, ISO 9001 QMS, R&D, technical), and Marketing. I was in the plastic packaging, natural rubber processing and commercial explosives industries. Academically, I have an MBA (specialisation in Finance) from UPM (CGPA 3.9 / 4.0) and a Bachelor of Chemical Engineering degree (Second Upper Honours) from UK.

### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Full Name: Lee, Woei Pena

Gender: Male

Date of Birth: 25 June 1976 Age: 38 years old

Marital status: Married

Children: Two sons (6 years old; 5 years old)

Nationality: Malaysian

Address: 21, Jalan Suasana 4/4

Bandar Tun Hussein Onn 43200 Cheras, Selangor

Tel No: 03 – 9075 1161 H/P No: 016 – 630 8169 E-mail: wpleessl@yahoo.com

Hobbies: Reading, watching movies, trying to get some exercise, and goofing with my sons

### **EDUCATION**

### Putra Business School, University Putra Malaysia, Serdang, Malaysia

Dates: From Sept 2011 to April 2013

Degree course: Master of Business Administration

Specialisation: Finance CGPA: 3.922 out of 4.000

# University of Bath, Bath, United Kingdom

Dates: From Sept 1995 to June 1999

Degree course and title: Chemical and Bio Process Engineering, B.Eng. (Hons)

Class: Second Class Honours First Division

### Taylor's College, Subang Jaya, Malaysia

Dates: From Jan 1994 to June 1995

Examination: Cambridge Board A-Level (Maths, Physics, Chemistry) and O-Level (General Paper)

Examination results: All A's

### Victoria Institution, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Dates: From Jan 1989 to Dec 1993

Examination: Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)

Examination results: 6 A1, 2 A2 (Grade 1, Aggregate 6)

### **DISTINCTIONS AND AWARDS**

# **University Education**

Bath University Accommodation Award, 1995 BP Chemicals Safety and Environment Prize, 1996

Dow Corning Award for meritorious laboratory performance, 1997

#### **Secondary Education**

Top SPM Science Stream Student, 1993

Full Colours as the Chairman of the Red Crescent Society, 1993



LEE WOEI PENG Curriculum Vitae

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## From Sept 2011 to April 2013

MBA at Putra Business School, University Putra Malaysia

From June 2010 to May 2011

Job Title / Employer: Group Asst Sales Manager, Versatile Creative Berhad & subsidiary Fairpoint

Plastics Sdn. Bhd.

Job Responsibilities: I was transferred to one of Versatile's subsidiaries Fairpoint Plastic Industries

after the previous marketing personnel had left. 70% of Fairpoint's business was with Nestle. The job required servicing the accounts which included product developments, and some new business developments. I also contributed in operational matters as I have experience in factory

management.

Reason for leaving: Further study (MBA).

From Nov 2007 to Nov 2009

Job Title / Employer: Business Development Manager, Medicplas Industries Sdn. Bhd.

Job Responsibilities: Overseeing the sales & marketing activities to ensure customers' orders

were delivered as per schedule and meeting the product quality specifications; developing new businesses with existing and new customers.

Major Achievements: The sales under my portfolio had doubled from RM 0.5 million to RM 1.0

million per month.

Reason for leaving: Limited career progression.

From May 2005 to March 2007

Job Title / Employer: Assistant Factory Manager, Mardec Berhad

Job Responsibilities: Assisting the Senior Factory Manager in controlling the profitability of the

processing plant operations, delivery requirements, quality control & assurance, and compliance to the statutory & regulatory requirements.

Major Achievements: Established the benchmark in the Internal QC lab setup among the other

Mardec factories, improvised the ISO 9001:2000 QMS (ZERO non-

compliance), and compliance to the DOSH & DOE requirements.

Reason for leaving: Returned to Klang Valley to start my family (this position was based in

Mentakab, Pahang).

From Oct 2000 to March 2005

Job Title / Employer: Assistant Technical Manager, Tenaga Kimia Berhad

Job Responsibilities: Overseeing the QAQC / R&D functions, supporting the Sales and Marketing

department through technical marketing activities (preparation of tender documents, supply estimates), providing consultation services for customers

(blasting designs, products applications).

Major Achievements: Developed a new product for the underground blasting, developed new

formulations and sourced new raw material suppliers, which contributed to 10% unit cost reduction, i.e. approximately RM 1 million then. Involvement in the blasting works of the MMCEG – Gamuda's SMART (Stormwater Management and Road Tunnel) Project in KL, securing the supply contract to Advocet Gold Mine in Kuala Lipis and Bakun Hydroelectric Dam Project in

Bintulu.

Reason for leaving: Hazardous job nature (explosive industry).

LEE WOEI PENG Curriculum Vitae

# **REFEREE**

Referee # 1 Referee # 2

Name: Prof Dato Dr Zulkifli Idris Mr Tan Kiau

Relationship: Former Lecturer at Putra Business Former Senior Factory Manager at

School, UPM, Serdang Mardec, Mentakab

Contact number: + 6012 281 3343 + 6012 740 3779

Email: drzulidris@gmail.com tankiau@hotmail.com

# **LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY**

SpokenWrittenEnglishFluentExcellentBahasa MalaysiaFluentVery good

Mandarin Fluent -

Cantonese Fluent -

# **LAST DRAWN SALARY**

RM 6,000 per month package in year 2011

# **EXPECTED SALARY**

RM 7,000 per month package